《绝望主妇》前情提要
Previously on Desperate Housewives
我离开莫蒂了
I left Morty.
苏珊的母亲经历了次刻骨铭心
Susan's mother made quite an impression.
布里定下了秘密约定
Bre made a secret commitment.
他不会让我们做朋友的
He's not gonna let us be friends.
谁说他知道我怎么度过我的闲暇时光
Well, who says he has to know how I spend my free time?
加布丽尔有了个发现
Gabrielle made a discovery.
我怀孕了 都是你的错
I am pregnant and it's all your fault.
汤姆犯了个错误
Tom made a mistake.
你居然雇佣了你的前女友
You hire your old girlfriend
还瞒了我整整3个月
and don't tell me about it for three months?
苏珊进行了一次委托
And Susan made an appointment...
你能帮我吗
Do you think you can help? ...
也惹上了麻烦
with trouble.
我能办到
I know I can.
从小
When she was younger,
苏菲·布雷默就是个无可救药的浪漫主义者
Sophie Bremmer was a hopeless romantic.
也天真得无与伦比
She was also hopelessly naive,
所以她结了四次婚
which is how she came to be married four times.
第一次她嫁给了个赌鬼
The first time to a man who liked to gamble.
第二次嫁给了个酒鬼
The second time to a man who liked to drink.
第三次嫁给了个同志
The third time to a man who liked other men.
而第四次
And the fourth time
她又嫁给了第二任
to the same man she married the second time.
没错 苏菲厌倦了一次次的心碎
Yes, Sophie was tired of having her heart broken.
所以她决定再也不结婚了
So she decided she would never get married again.
而这天晚上
And then one night...
苏菲
Sophie! ...
来了一位访客
She had a visitor.
苏菲
Sophie!
莫蒂 你在干什么
Morty, what are you doing?
我要跟苏菲谈谈
I-I-I need to talk to Sophie.
现在 你醉了吗
Now? Are you drunk?
一点点
Uh... Just a little.
你好吗 苏珊
H-how are you, Susie?
我得 跟苏菲聊聊
I've got... I've got to speak to uh... to Sophie.
现在是凌晨1点 她已经睡了
It's 1 o'clock in the morning and she is sleeping.
我要向她求婚
I'm gonna ask her to marry me.
-什么 -我觉得我会幸福的
- What? - Well, I thought I could be happy.
餐馆赚了些小钱
The restaurant is starting to make money.
我刚买了部水上摩托艇
I just bought a new jet ski.
胆固醇也降下来了
My cholesterol is down.
可没有她 一切都没意义
But none of it's any fun without her.
莫蒂 我觉得这不太可能
Oh, Morty. I just don't think it's going to happen.
她已经想重新开始了 你先坐吧
She's moved on. Why don't you just sit down?
我去帮你叫辆出租车
I'm gonna call you a cab.
-苏菲 -医生告诉过你别喝酒了
- Sophie. - Your doctor told you not to drink.
有时候你需要点
Well, there are times when you need uh...
你需要点酒来壮胆
when you need liquid courage.
这戒指是德洛丽丝的吗
Did this ring belong to Dolores?
你把亡妻的戒指给她
You gave her your dead wife's ring?
这可是枚三爪钻戒
It's a three-carat diamond.
她不该介意这是不是用过的
She shouldn't care if it's used.
苏菲 你愿意吗
So what... what do you say, Soph?
-好吧 -真的
- All right. - Really?
-真的 -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
只不过 你得稍微正式点
But no... You've got to do it officially. You know...
好的 给你
Yeah. Oh um... Here.
苏菲 你愿意嫁给我吗
Sophie, would you do me the honor of marrying me?
苏菲·布雷默依然是个
Sophie Bremmer was still
无可救药的浪漫主义者
a hopeless romantic.
有个条件
On one condition.
明天我们去把这个钻戒换掉
Tomorrow we trade this in for a ring of my own.
我要自己的钻戒比德洛丽丝的大
And I want a bigger diamond than Dolores got.
但她可不再天真了
But she was no longer naive.
《绝望的主妇》第一季 第二十一集
Desperate Housewives S01E21
婚姻是个简单的概念
Marriage is a simple concept.
根本上 就是两人订下合同
Basically, it's a contract betwen two people
确保他们携手一生
that binds them together for life
希冀从此过上幸福快乐的生活
in the hopes that they can live happily ever after.
不幸的是 有的合同 就快失效了
Sadly, some contracts... are made to be broken.
-我没破坏你的避孕计划 -是吗
- I didn't mess with your birth control. - Really?
真的
Really.
这明显是被撕开又放回去了
Look. It's been pulled apart and put back together.
也可能是生产时的纰漏
It's probably a manufacturing defect.
还能看到胶水痕迹
You can still see the glue marks.
反正 不是我干的
I'm telling you, I didn't do it.
我不傻 卡洛斯
Don't insult me, Carlos.
这些个月你一直在念叨孩子的事
You've been whining about wanting a baby for months.
除了你还有谁会这么干
Who else would it have been?
我没有
I don't...
-不 -怎么了
- Oh, no. - What?
-是妈妈 -别扯了
- Mama. - Oh, Please.
完全有可能
It's possible.
你都是半年买一次这种药 对吧
You buy that stuff in bulk, six months at a time, right?
是啊 所以呢
Yeah. So?
出事之前
Before the accident,
我告诉她我很想有个孩子
I told her how much I wanted to have a child.
她说她来搞定
She said that she would take care of it.
我以为她是要跟你谈谈
I just thought that she would talk to you.
宝贝 我很抱歉
Baby, I am so sorry.
那个死女人
That bitch.
真难以置信
I can't believe her.
我爱她 可有时我也觉得她不太好
I loved her but even I had issues sometimes.
她太有控制欲
She could be very controlling.
从坟墓里爬出来掐住我
Reaching out from the grave to screw with me.
天啊 她真是好样的
God, she's good.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我感觉要晨吐了
I feel a wave of morning sickness coming on.
我想吐的时候正好站在你妈的坟上
I want to be standing on your mother's grave when it hits.
我今天回家会晚点
I'm gonna be home late tonight.
彼德森想跟我们出去喝几杯
Peterson wants to take us out for drinks.
好的
Oh, that's fine. Uh...
我想跟你说点事
I wanted to talk to you about something.
什么
What?
他们来等你了
Oh, that's your car pool.
你先去吧 没事
You gotta go. Never mind.
-勒奈特 什么事 -没什么
- Lynette, what is it? - It's nothing.
好吧
Ok.
这只是
It's just...
我们十天没做爱了
We haven't had sex in ten days.
之前最长纪录是九天
The longest we've ever gone before is nine.
我们不是上周四才做过吗
Didn't we do it last Thursday?
我们刚要开始 你就睡着了
We started to but then... you fell asleep.
这就是你焦虑的原因
Is this why you're so worried?
要是你想 我们今晚就能做
We can do it tonight if you want to.
-随便啦 -不 我都压抑十天了
- Whatever. - No, I've got ten days pent up in me.
我们今晚做
We are doing it tonight.
别担心了 好吗
You have nothing to worry about, ok?
糟糕 我忘拿公文包
Oh, crap. I forgot my briefcase.
替我告诉他们我马上就来
Can you tell them I'll be right there?
没问题
Sure.
勒奈特
Hey, Lynette.
汤姆准备好了吧
So is Tom almost ready?
是的 他去拿公文包了
Yeah, he's just getting his briefcase.
不好意思
Sorry.
没事
It's ok.
-拜拜 -拜拜
- Bye. - Bye.
我能行 我能行
I got it. I got it.
谢谢你收留我
Thank you for having me.
我会想念你们的
I'm gonna miss you both so much.
我们也是 没有你家里好安静
Us too. The house will feel just empty without you.
-你们就不能多待几天吗 -不
- Can't you guys stay a little longer? - No, no, no.
他们想马上开始新生活
They wanna get their new life started.
我们可不想拖这些小情人的后腿
We don't wanna hold these crazy kids back.
拜拜 莫蒂
Bye, Morty.
我希望这没事
Uh... Listen, I hope it's ok
但你母亲告诉了我一些
but your mom told me some of the stuff
你经历的事情
that you've been going through,
就是跟这条街上那个水管工的事情
you know, with the plumber guy across the street.
-她说了 -是的
- She did, huh? - Yeah. Um...
别放弃他
Don't give up on him.
要知道 要是我放弃了
I mean, if I'd given up,
我现在就不会跟这位可爱的熟女在一起了
I wouldn't be here now with this lovely lady.
她告诉你
Did she tell you
他因为过失杀人而蹲过大牢吗
that he served time in prison for manslaughter?
没有 她遗漏了这部分
No, she left that part out.
估计她也没告诉你他还是个毒贩子
I don't suppose she told you he was a drug dealer.
这我记不清了
I don't recall that.
别这样 你并不知道整件事
Will you stop? You don't know the whole story.
-妈 -我跟他说了你有多爱他
- Mother... - I told him how much you love him.
什么 你怎么想的
What? What were you thinking?
-那他怎么说 -是啊 他怎么说
- What did he say? - Yeah, what did he say?
我想我提得非常不合时宜
I think I walked in on him at a very bad time.
跟他亲近的某人刚刚去世了
Someone close to him had just died.
上帝 真的吗
Oh, god. Really?
他需要一个可以哭泣的肩膀
He could use a shoulder to cry on.
再抱一下好吗 拜托了 我舍不得你
Can I have one more hug? Please. I can't stand it.
乔治 你一定要尝尝这个
Oh, George. You have got to taste this.
-模样不太好 -我等不及了
- A little messy but... - I can't wait.
是茴香籽吗 非常馥郁可口
Mm. Is that fennel seed? It's fantastic.
不知道 但如此的美味总透着点罪恶
I don't know, but anything that good has got to be sinful.
试试不同的食物
Isn't this fun trying different dishes
来点新体验很有趣吧
and opening up to new experiences?
雷克斯讨厌所谓的美食之旅
Rex just hates these cooks tours.
他宁愿呆在家里
He likes to stay at home
吃意大利面 配上一大杯根汁汽水
with a plate of spaghetti and a mug of root beer.
这意式番茄酱怎么样
So how about this Marinara Sauce?
这是我吃过最好吃的
I think it's the best I've ever had.
我吃过更好的 不过是在意大利
I had one better but that was in Italy.
你去过意大利吗
You've been to Italy?
雷克斯和我去那度假
Rex and I took a vacation there
那时孩子们还没出生
right before the kids were born.
结婚头几年我们很幸福
We had so much fun in those first few years.
那时我很容易就能重新开心起来
Guess it was just easier to be happy back then.
我怎么说起这个 我不该再喝了
I don't know why I just said that. No more wine for me.
也许我们应该去意大利
Maybe we should go to Italy.
-什么 -那一定很震撼
- What? - Wouldn't that be a hoot?
那儿有博物馆 大教堂 还有餐馆
All those museums and cathedrals and trattorias.
我们可以尽情玩个够
We could just make pigs of ourselves.
我不能和你去旅行 乔治
I can't go on a trip with you, George.
为什么
Why not?
我是有夫之妇 人们会闲言碎语
I'm married. People would talk.
对 很抱歉 这主意很糟
Right. I'm sorry. It was a bad idea.
别多想了
Don't worry about it.
试试这个蛤蚌
Here. I want you to try one of these clams.
我敢打赌它跟番茄酱一样美味
I bet they're as good as the Marinara Sauce.
你说得很对
You are absolutely right.
美好的事物总是透着点罪恶
If it's that good, it's just got to be sinful.
孩子们 现在7点了
Ok, boys. It's 7:00.
该睡觉了 走吧
It's time for bed. Excuse me. Let's go.
为什么要那么早就睡
Why do we have to go to bed so early?
我告诉过你们 宝贝
I told you, honey.
爸爸和我今晚有个特别约会
Daddy and I have a special meeting tonight.
快去
Go on.
我爱你们
I love you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
好吧 第十天了
Hi. Whoa. All right. This is the tenth day.
亲爱的 稍等会儿 让我脱掉工作服
Honey, give me a second to let the office wear off.
-好 -好 我来了
- Ok. - Ok, I'm in.
想什么呢
What are you thinking?
我在想那是什么味道
I was wondering what that smell was.
很可能是宝宝的口水
It's probably baby drool.
行了 这下好了吧
There. Now you have easier access.
来啦
Incoming!
-怎么了 -那味道好像渗进去了
- What? - Well, that smell really soaked through, huh?
没错 是有点渗进去
Yes. It soaked through a little.
婴儿吐奶就是这样
That is the nature of baby throw-up.
不见得要我穿防护服吧
Do you want me to wear a hazmat suit?
不 我只是喜欢你干干净净的
No, I just like it when you're all clean
穿着性感的衣服
and in your sexy clothes.
我可没什么干净的 性感的衣服
I don't own anything clean and sexy.
每件衣服上不是有婴儿的口水
Everything is either covered in baby spit
就是有化开的蜡笔印
or chunks of melted crayon.
对不起
Ok, I'm sorry.
你让我觉得自己像从捕虾船下来似的
You make me feel like I just got off the shrimp boat.
宝贝 我说了对不起
Honey, I said I'm sorry.
只是男人有时候喜欢
It's just that guys sometimes like it when women,
女人稍微打扮一下
you know, put a little effort into things.
好了
Ok. Um...
要不我们还是接着亲吻吧 试试看
Can we just go back to the kissing thing? Can we try that.
好
Fine.
-算了 -宝宝醒了
- Ok. Off. - Oh, the baby's up!
妈妈
Mom!
-苏珊·梅尔雇了你吗 -我知道
- Susan Mayer hired you? - I know. Huh.
她决定不再亲自刺探你的事
She decided to stop poking around in your life
却偏偏挑中了我
and call me of all people.
你真走运 我的广告在黄页上很显眼
Lucky for you, I've got the biggest ad in the phone book.
-我该怎么办 -跑
- What am I going to do? - Run.
-带上你的孩子走人 -那不好办
- Pack up your kid and get out of town. - That's tricky.
我儿子不愿意走
My son doesn't want to move.
他非常固执
He can be pretty insistent.
我可以暂时引开她的注意
Well, I can throw her off the scent for a while.
行
Fine.
那好
All right then.
告诉我你想让她以为是怎么回事
Tell me exactly what it is you want this woman to believe.
她本名是安吉拉
She was born Angela,
不过她十几岁时
but when she was a teenager
把自己的名字改成了玛丽·艾莉丝
she changed her name to Mary Alice.
申请表上说
The application says
她的名字是照一个亲戚的名字起的
that she was named after a relative
但她跟那亲戚绝交了
that she no longer speaks to.
这是她的出生证明
Now, here's her birth certificate
还有她在犹他州依法改名的申请
and her Utah petition for a legal name change.
丹娜是怎么回事
What about Dana?
记录显示有另一个孩子
There was a record of another child.
是个名叫丹娜·玛丽·杨的女孩
A girl. Dana Marie Young,
1岁半时死了 应该是摔死的
died at 18 months, apparently from some kind of fall.
他说的都是真的
It was all true. Everything he said.
我怎么错得这么离谱
How could I have been so wrong?
-给我开支票吧 -当然
- I'm gonna need a check. - Oh. Of course.
事实上 你走之前
Actually, before you go,
我要你帮忙查查另一个人的背景
I need you to check into someone else's background.
就是我认识的这个水管工
There's this plumber I know.
收到我的留言了吗
Hey. Did you get my messages?
收到了 我没给你回电话
Yeah, I didn't want to call you back
因为我想和你见面谈
'cause I wanted to talk to you in person.
我要跟你说件比较麻烦的事
I have some potentially upsetting news.
说吧 索利斯夫人
Come on, Mrs. Solis.
跟我说吧 我能搞定
You can tell me. I can handle it.
我怀孕了 孩子可能是你的
I'm pregnant and it might be yours.
我连摩托车都买不了
I could barely afford my new dirt bike.
我怎么养得起孩子
How am I gonna handle child support?
还没确定是不是你的 放松点
We don't know for sure if it's yours, so relax.
-我不是来看你的惊吓样 -那是为了什么
- I didn't come to watch you freak out. - Why did you come?
我想确保你让我保护你不被伤害
I want to make sure you let me protect you.
谁会伤害我
From who?
卡洛斯 还有你父母
Carlos, your parents.
约翰 这事会毁了你的人生
John, something like this can ruin your life.
所以咱俩的事你一定得保密
That's why you have to keep quiet about our affair.
没必要把咱俩都卷进这场灾难
There's no point in this catastrophe taking both of us down.
-谢谢 -忘掉它吧
- Thank you. - Forget about it.
-我该戴安全套的 -是的
- I should have worn a condom. - Yeah.
那会很有帮助
That would have been helpful.
你雇了个私家侦探
You hired a private investigator?
我不能相信麦克
I can't trust Mike
我想知道究竟发生了什么
and I want to find out what really happened.
所以就得通过没有企图的外人
From a source that doesn't have an agenda.
打开它
Now open it up.
好 准备好了吗
Ok. You ready?
开始吧
Go.
-停 -什么
- Stop! - What?
如果你真发现了什么坏事
Ok. If you find out something that's really bad,
也尽量说得好听些
just try to put a positive spin on it.
好了
Ok.
有好消息 也有坏消息
I have some good news and some bad news.
先告诉我坏消息
Give me the bad news first.
麦克杀的那人 是个警察
The guy Mike killed... was a cop.
天哪
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god.
行了 好消息呢
Ok. Give me the good news.
-没有好消息 -什么
- There is none. - What?
你让我说得好听些
You told me to spin it!
算了 我自己看吧
Oh, forget it. Just let me look at it myself.
[毒贩袭警]
[众人哀悼斯莱警官]
-难以置信 -怎么了
- I can't believe it. - What is it?
我认识她
I know her.
怎么回事
What's going on here?
你们俩还不罢手 是不是
You two just won't stop, will you?
黛德丽已经死了
Deidre's dead.
是谁杀的她已经无关紧要了
It doesn't matter who killed her.
-让这事过去吧 -没那么容易 凯德拉
- Just let it go. - It's not that easy, Kendra.
为什么 我妹妹恨你们 你们俩都恨
Why? My sister hated you. Both of you.
-她自己说的 -那是毒品的关系
- She said so. - That was the drugs talking.
是啊是啊 毒品
Right, right. The drugs.
黛德丽让家人蒙羞
Deidre humiliated this family
她对我们的关心不屑一顾
and she threw our love back in our faces.
她很清楚这一点 而且毫不在乎
She knew it and she couldn't have cared less.
-你说完了吗 -没有
- Are you done? - No.
我想知道你们在计划什么
I want to know what you're planning.
-我们只是聊天而已 -我不信
- We're just talking. - I don't believe you.
那就别问了
Then don't ask.
我当然不想另找一个心脏病医生
Of course I don't want a new cardiologist
李已经做了好几周的检查
but Lee's been conducting tests for weeks.
可他至今还不知道哪里出了问题
He should have been able to know what's wrong by now.
亲爱的 我们和他们有交情
Honey, we socialize with them.
我该怎么对海伦说
What am I going to say to Helen?
我只知道 我从来没这么难受过
All I know is, I've never felt worse,
我必须采取行动
and I've got to do something.
我得去和伊迪聊两句
Um... I uh... I have to talk to Edie.
布里 我们要迟到了
Um... Bree, we're gonna be late.
只需一会 我要问个食谱
Oh, it'll just take a second. I need to um... get a recipe.
-伊迪 你好 -你好
- Edie. Hi. - Hi.
昨天我在费雷多餐厅看到你了
I saw you at Fredo's yesterday.
我也看见你了
Yeah, I saw you, too.
调皮啊 真调皮
Naughty, naughty.
-你说什么 -那个家伙
- I beg your pardon? - The guy.
你喂他吃东西的那个
The one you were spoon-feeding.
还不错 虽然对我来说弱了点
Not bad. A little petit for my taste,
但又不是我要跟他睡
but then again I'm not the one sleeping with him.
我就担心你会往这方面想
This is exactly what I was afraid of.
乔治和我只是朋友
George and I are just friends.
我并不是在损你 我明白的
Hey, I'm not judging you. I get it.
雷克斯和那个道貌岸然的妓女有染
Rex was sticking it to that hooker housewife.
该是你报仇的时候了
It's payback time.
完全不是你想的那样
You have got the wrong idea.
那个男人是我的药剂师
That man is my pharmacist.
那么多人 你偏偏找个药剂师
You could have an affair with anyone. You choosed a pharmacist?
你还真是个共和党人
You are such a republican.
我没搞婚外情
I am not having an affair.
乔治和我 我们就聊聊天
George and I, we just talk.
他是个很好的倾听者
He's a very good listener
我能跟他谈我的抱负 我的梦想
and I share my hopes and dreams with him,
以及我内心最隐秘的想法
and my innermost thoughts.
仅仅如此 你得相信我
That's all there is to it and you have to believe me.
-没问题 我相信你 -谢谢
- Ok. I believe you. - thank you.
我很高兴能把这件事澄清
I'm glad we cleared this up.
你肯定觉得这很古怪
I know it must have looked strange
但我不想你觉得
and I didn't want you to think
我对我丈夫不忠
that I was cheating on my husband.
但你的确有点不忠了
But you sort of are.
-什么 -别否认了 布里
- Excuse me? - Well, come on, bree.
你都把内心最隐秘的想法告诉他了
You're telling him your innermost thoughts?
你的抱负 你的梦想
Your hopes? Your dreams?
除了没性关系
Sex aside,
你跟一个不是自己丈夫的男人那么亲密
you're pretty intimate with a guy that's not your husband.
每个人都需要有可以说说话的人
Well, I mean, everybody needs someone to talk to.
那为什么不对雷克斯说说呢
What's wrong with talking to Rex?
我们不在家 请留言
We are not at home. Please leave a message.
你好 是扎克吗
Hello, Zach?
我是费莉西娅·蒂尔曼
It's Felicia Tillman.
我实在很喜欢我们的小聚会
I do so enjoy our little visits
也有好几天没见着你了
and I haven't seen you for a few days.
我希望你一切还好
I hope everything's all right.
扎克最近身体不舒服
Zach's not feeling well.
是你 保罗
Oh. Paul.
另外他一直在你家叨扰不太合适
And I don't think it's appropriate that he spends so much time at your house.
我弄了点热可可 今天感觉如何
Made us some cocoa. How are you feeling?
这两天我觉得很难受
I've felt awful for two days now.
我该去看医生吗
Think I should see a doctor?
你可能只是得了流感
It's probably just a touch of the flu.
看看你的情况再说
We'll keep an eye on it.
恐怕是因为这房子 我也不太舒服
It's this house, Zach. I feel it too.
待在这里对我们俩都不好
It isn't healthy for us to stay here.
我已经说过了 我不会走的
I told you. I'm not moving.
这样是为了你好
It would be for your own good.
你不能再这样下去
You can't keep doing the kinds of things you're doing.
像在苏珊·梅尔家的厨房表现得那样
Susan Mayer's kitchen, for example.
人们会渐渐发现的
People are going to catch on.
换个环境重新开始不好吗
Wouldn't it be great to start over somewhere in the country?
你会交到新朋友 也许新的女朋友
Could meet some new friends. Maybe even meet a new girl.
就这样睡吧
How about I let you sleep on it?
我们明天再谈搬家的事
We'll talk about moving tomorrow.
婚姻中缺乏激情
The lack of passion in her marriage
对勒奈特来说已是不幸的现实
had become an unpleasant reality for Lynette.
突然有一天她想到
Then one day it occurred to her,
改变这现实最好的办法...
The best way to fight reality...
就是来点不现实的
was with a little fantasy.
当然 如果没人来欣赏的话
Of course, all the fantasy
那世上所有的不现实表演...
in the world won't do you any good...
都不会带给你任何好处
if no one shows up to enjoy it.
汤姆 抱歉给你添麻烦了
I feel bad about putting you out like this, Tom.
你没给我添麻烦
You're not putting anybody out.
你一整天都在外忙
You've been flying all day.
再随便住个旅店就太辛苦了
Why stay in some hotel?
你不介意睡我家沙发就好
I just hope you don't mind sleeping on the sofa.
你们家沙发真不错
Yeah. Sofa should be fine.
亲爱的 你干嘛不...
Hey, honey. Why don't you just...
让咱家的女仆来干这些呢
let the maid get that?
一点也不好笑 汤姆
Not funny, Tom.
对了 加里在冲澡
Oh, by the way. Gary's showering.
他要块干净的毛巾
He asked if you could bring him a clean towel
能麻烦你骑着扫把给他送去吗
and your riding crop.
别生气
Come on!
没有 我很乐意你拿我的糗事开心
No, I'm glad that you find my humiliation so entertaining.
亲爱的 你昨天就是一副法国女仆打扮
Honey, you were wearing a French maid's costume.
说吧 你昨天想干什么
I mean, come on. What were you thinking?
我在想我们的婚姻出现了问题
I was thinking that our marriage was in trouble
我们俩中至少有人得去挽救
and one of us should try and save it.
我们婚姻什么时候出现问题了
Whoa. Since when is our marriage in trouble?
是 我们有些日子没做过爱了
Ok, so we haven't had sex for a few days.
的确 是个问题
Big deal. It happens.
正好 是安娜贝尔 多讽刺啊
Oh. That's Annabel. How ironic.
安娜贝尔和我们说的有什么关系
How is Aannabel relevant to this conversation?
因为每天早上她走进这间屋子
Because she comes to this house
都在提醒你我不够...
every morning to remind you of what I'm not...
不够什么
what?
汤姆 她多么令人充满幻想
She's the fantasy, Tom.
这样一个手指纤纤 身穿名牌套装
The hot woman that you work with every day
且热辣的尤物和你一起工作
with her manicured nails and her designer outfits.
而我就是现实
I am the reality.
一个素面朝天的妻子
The wife who never wears makeup
身上散发着脏衣服篓子的味道
and whose clothes smell like a hamper.
这也许是你说过最蠢的话
Ok, this may be the stupidest thing you've ever said.
我过去也让人充满幻想
I used to be the fantasy.
那时我不用弄一套女仆装
There was a time when I didn't need a maid's outfit
因为我知道就算我穿着有怪味的汗衫
because I knew I was enough for you.
我依旧对你充满吸引力
Even wearing a smelly t-shirt.
但很显然 世易时移
And clearly, that's no longer the case.
亲爱的 我不知道该怎么说
Ok, honey, I don't know what to say.
如果我能做些什么让你不这样想
If there's a way for me to fix this,
我会做的
I will do it.
告诉我 我会办到
Just tell me and I will do it.
不 根本没什么办法
No, there's nothing to fix.
我是说 我们都变了
We've changed. That's all I'm saying.
走吗
You ready?
去吧 你也不想让安娜贝尔等太久
You should go. You don't want to keep Annabel waiting.
少加点辣 孩子的小心脏会烧痛的
Be careful with that. You'll give the baby heartburn.
我吃不出味道
I can't get it hot enough.
荷尔蒙失调让我的味觉都失灵了
My hormones are killing my taste buds.
现在你对食物的兴趣
You've been paying more attention to your food
比对我的兴趣还大
than you have to me lately.
我要变得够胖才对得起你妈妈
I plan on getting really fat as a tribute to your mother.
约翰 你来这做什么
John, what are you doing here?
我一直在想孩子的事
I've been thinking about the baby.
是吗 为什么
Really? Why?
他很有可能是我的孩子
There's a good chance that it's mine.
我想做我该做的
I want to do the right thing.
不 你没什么该做的事
No... Nobody expects you to do the right thing.
我就知道你想让我走
I kind of figured you'd try to blow me off.
所以我直接去找索利斯先生
That's why I'm going directly to Mr. Solis.
什么 你疯了吗 他会杀了我们俩
What? Are you crazy? He would kill us both.
他和我得解决这件事 以男人的方式
He and I need to hash this out. Man to man.
-这才是对孩子最好的 -约翰
- It's what's best for the baby. - John!
是你去叫他 还是我去
Are you gonna go get him or am I?
好吧 听你的
Ok. You win.
在这等着
Wait right here.
-别出来 -为什么
- Uh... Don't get out. - why?
因为我正准备进来
Because I was going to get in.
要知道 怀孕的女人如狼似虎
Yeah. You see, pregnant women have very strong urges.
好的
All right.
我脱了衣服马上就来
I'm gonna freshen up and I'll be right back.
-好的 -你先泡着
- Ok. - You sit.
坐好 我去开点音乐
Sit. I'm turning on some music.
卡洛斯现在没空
Um... Carlos is unavailable at the moment.
-你说谎 -约翰 你到底要干什么
- You're lying. - John, what are you doing?
-索利斯先生 开门 -别叫了
- Mr. Solis... open up! - Stop it!
你要... 约翰
What are you... John!
-索利斯夫人 让开 -你干什么
- Mrs. Solis, get out of the way...- What are you doing?
不
No!
我的天哪
Oh, my god!
-好辣 -对不起 是酸辣酱
- Oh, god, it burns. - I'm sorry. It's just salsa.
-简直像硫酸 -我不知道它这么刺激
- It feels like acid. - I've been finding it so bland.
索利斯先生 索利斯先生 出来
Mr. Solis! Mr. Solis! Come out here.
-我要和您谈谈 -约翰 闭嘴
- I need to talk to you! - John, shut up!
约翰 给我闭嘴 听我说
John, shut the hell up. Listen to me.
你永远不可能成为这个孩子的父亲
You are never gonna be the father of this baby.
不管亲子鉴定的结果是什么
No matter what the paternity tests say,
他都是卡洛斯的孩子
it's Carlos' child.
你怎么能这么说
How can you say that?
因为卡洛斯养得起这个孩子 约翰
Because Carlos can provide, John.
他能给孩子需要的一切
He will give this baby everything.
上钢琴课 去夏令营 读最好的大学
Piano lessons and summer camp and the best colleges.
他能给孩子提供应有的成长环境
He can raise this child the way a child deserves to be raised.
而你不能
You can't.
这不是钱的问题
This isn't about money.
而是怎样才算为孩子好
This is about what's best for the baby.
如果你想给这个孩子最好的 你得帮我
If you want what's best for the baby, then you will help me.
帮我让这个孩子别像我这样穷苦地长大
Help me make sure this kid does not grow up poor like I did.
你怎么这么久呀...
What's taking you...
你好 约翰
Oh, hey, John.
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
他是来...
Um... He...
贾斯丁想把绣球花换了
Justin thinks the hydrangeas need replacing.
他要听听我的意见
He wanted me to come by for a second opinion.
你朋友是个好孩子 但他不及你一半
Youre friend's a good kid, but he's not half the gardener you were.
你应该回来继续为我们工作
You should come back and work for us.
你就像是我们的家人
You're practically family.
谢谢 索利斯先生
Thanks, Mr. Solis.
扎克 你在吗
Zach? Are you here?
我不得不这么做 宝贝
I have to do this, dear.
我知道你会原谅我的
I know you'll forgive me.
[保罗 扎克在我这 费莉西娅]
-小子们都睡了吗 -早睡着了
- Are the boys asleep? - Tucked in tight.
-佩妮呢 -睡得正香
- And Penny? - Sound asleep.
等这闹钟停了 到卧室找我
Ok, when this thing goes off, meet me in the bedroom.
你这是干什么
What are you... What is this...
耐心点 等钟停了
Uh-uh. Wait till it goes off.
好啦 我进来啦
All right. I'm coming in.
上帝啊
Oh, my god!
你不是想要刺激吗 这够刺激了吧
You want fantasy? I give you fantasy.
过来 女人 准备投降吧
Come to me, woman, and prepare to be boarded.
动作快点
Please, will you make it fast?
这东西太紧了
These things are just chafing.
我还真挺喜欢这个
I uh... I kinda like it.
好 把灯关了
Good. Kill the lights.
-不要 -关了吧
- No. - Please.
-不关灯 -关了吧
- Not turning off the lights. - Please.
我偏不
No, no, no.
门没锁
It's open.
保罗 是你 见到你真高兴
Oh, Paul, it's you. I'm so glad.
我有点东西给你看
I have some papers I want you to look at.
-我儿子在哪 -楼上
- Where's my son? - Upstairs.
吃了你喂的镇定剂 正睡呢
Sleeping off those tranquilizers you gave him.
我不知道你打什么注意
I don't know what you think you're doing
但我要带我儿子走
but I'm taking my son and going.
我和我妹妹不一样 保罗
I am not my sister, Paul.
惹毛我有你好看的
You do not want to screw with me.
玛莎有份流水帐
Martha kept a journal.
乏味生活的点点滴滴
Every drab event of her drab life
她都备份了
meticulously documented.
包括她发现你和你妻子
Including her discovery that you and your wife
偷了个孩子
stole a baby.
一个叫丹娜的孩子
A baby named Dana.
抱歉这副本可能不是很清楚
I'm sorry if the copies are hard to read.
我把原件藏在了一个安全的地方
I hid the originals in a safe place.
鉴于你杀了玛莎和种种行为
It seemed like a reasonable precaution,
这种预防措施必不可少
since you murdered Martha and all.
吃曲奇吗
Would you like a cookie?
自便吧
Suit yourself.
其实我有个小提议
Now, I have a little proposition for you.
这不过是一个孤独寂寞的女人凭空臆想
These are the fantasies of a bored, lonely woman.
证明不了什么
They prove nothing.
警察到现在还没来抓你的唯一原因
The only reason the police haven't caught you yet
就是他们没理由怀疑你
is because they have no reason to suspect you.
一旦他们发现了
But once they found out
勒索过安吉... 抱歉 玛丽·艾莉丝
that Martha was blackmailing Ange, sorry, Mary Alice...
-你想要什么 -和你一样
- What is it you want? - The same thing you want.
要你离开这 改名换姓
For you to leave town, change your name,
在一个遥远的地方开始全新的生活
and start your life over again somewhere far away from here.
你这么有把握 干吗不直接去告发我
If you're so sure, why don't you just turn me in?
那样的话扎克永远不会原谅我
Because Zach would never forgive me.
而且他往后都要和我住
And it's important that we be on good terms,
咱俩关系不能搞僵了
seeing as how he's going to be living with me now.
-什么 -你东西都收拾好了
- What? - Your bags are packed.
你就要开始亡命天涯了
You're about to become a fugitive.
你想让你的儿子跟着受罪吗
Is that the life you want for your son?
想要两个人一起居无定所吗
The two of you spending every night in a different town?
不会的 你是个好父亲
No. You're a better father than that.
我不能就这么丢下他
I can't just leave him.
你把他偷来 让他过好日子
You stole him so that he could have a better life.
这行为很高尚 保罗 真的
That was a noble act, Paul. Truly.
是时候再发扬一次精神了
And it's time for you to be noble again.
道个别都不行吗
Can I at least say goodbye?
你给我机会和玛莎告别了吗
Did you allow me to say goodbye to Martha?
我想找凯德拉·泰勒
Oh, hi. I'm looking for Kendra Taylor.
对不起 请你离开
I'm sorry. You're gonna have to leave.
你不明白
Oh. Oh, you don't understand.
我不能就这么走
See, I can't just drive away.
-请回车里去 -听着 鲍勃
- Please get back in the car. - Look um... Bob.
-让我解释下 -回车里去
- Let me try to explain. - In the car.
是这样的 这可能是我
See, the thing is, this is maybe my last chance
寻回真爱的最后机会
to find out if I can be with the man I love.
-女士 -而且 鲍勃
- Ma'am... - And, Bob,
你不知道这对我有多重要
I can't begin to tell you how much that means to me.
所以我要径直走进那间房子
So I'm gonna walk up to that house
你不能阻拦我
and you're gonna let me.
知道为什么吗
And you know why?
因为在这个徽章
Because behind that badge
和这对雄健的胸肌后面
and that just big, you-could-crush-me-like-a-fly chest,
隐藏着一颗真心
there's a heart.
一颗相信爱情的心
A heart that believes in love.
滚回车里去
Just get in the damn car.
你天生缺爱又不是我的错
It's not my fault you don't have love in your life.
-苏珊 -凯德拉
- Susan? - Hi, Kendra.
看完这些证据之后
And despite the evidence that's been all laid out in front of me,
我觉得这后面肯定还有隐情
I can't help thinking there's more to the story.
-听起来很蠢吗 -不 一点也不
- Does it sound stupid? - No, no, of course not.
不幸的是 事实就这些 没什么隐情
Unfortunately, you've got the whole story right here.
但麦克的律师提出他是正当防卫
But Mike's lawyer pleaded self-defense,
那才是真相吧
if that's the case.
德尔菲诺卖海洛因给我女儿
Delfino sold black-tar heroin to my daughter.
杀了想抓他的警察
He killed the cop that tried to bust him,
被判有罪还坐牢了
got convicted and did his time.
-就这么简单 -爸
- End of story... - Dad...
不管真相多残忍 她都应该知道
She deserves to hear the truth, however awful.
真的很抱歉 梅尔女士
I'm sorry, Miss Mayer. I really am.
感谢你告诉我这些
I appreciate you talking to me.
你这算什么
What the hell was that?
要是她知道了真相
If she knew the truth,
肯定重新回到他的怀抱
she'd go running back to him.
那会干扰他完成任务
She might talk him out of doing his job.
不能冒这个险
I can't risk that.
我时日不多啦
Just don't have the time.
快 开到转角去 我们得谈谈
Quick. Drive around the corner. We need to talk.
雷克斯 你觉得绿色怎么样
What do you think? Rex, I chose green
那么不管加布丽尔生男生女都能穿
so it will work whether Gabrielle has a boy or a girl.
挺好的
That's great.
怎么了 整天都闷闷不乐
What's the matter? You've been mopey all day.
抱歉 我有点担心检查结果
I'm sorry. I'm just worried about the test results.
要是不快点知道问题在哪 我会发疯的
If I don't find out what's wrong with me soon, I'll lose my mind.
-亲爱的 -我把你唠叨烦了
- Oh, honey. - You must get tired of me complaining.
不是这样的
No. No, not at all.
我也觉得该谈谈这事
I think that we should talk about it.
实际上 我觉得我们俩沟通不够
In fact, I think maybe we don't talk enough.
可能吧
I guess.
我们该重新像情侣那样 凡事都一起做
Why don't we start doing things together again as a couple?
等你身体好些 我们就去度假
As soon as you're well enough, we should go on a vacation.
出去转转 找找乐子
Take a trip. Go somewhere fun.
-记得我们的意大利之行吗 -差不多
- Remember our trip to Italy? - Sort of.
差不多
Sort of?
你忘了那些美食和如画的风景吗
You don't remember the glorious food and the gorgeous scenery and...
我就记得当时汗出得像落汤鸡一样
What I remember is sweating like a pig
还后悔把积蓄都花光了
and wishing we hadn't spent all our savings.
你想去哪呢
So where would you like to go?
无所谓 你选吧
It doesn't matter. You decide.
麦克不是毒贩
Mike wasn't a drug dealer.
-什么 -黛德丽才是
- what? - Deidre was.
麦克很早就戒掉了
Mike, he kicked the habit early on.
但是黛德丽戒不掉 或是不想戒
But Deidre couldn't or didn't want to. I don't know.
最后她失控了
Anyway, she spiraled out of control
频繁入狱
and was in and out of jail.
一天一个便衣发现她吸毒
One day an undercover cop caught her using.
就逼她用性交易来换取自由
He forced her to trade sex for freedom.
麦克后来发现了
Look, Mike found out about it
想阻止这事
and he tried to put a stop to it.
他撞到他俩在一起
He busted in on the two of them.
警察用枪指着他
He... Well, the cop pulled a gun on him
但被麦克打倒了
and Mike fought him off,
他俩一起从阳台摔下去了
But they both went over the balcony.
只有麦克活了下来
Mike was the only one that got back up.
那就是正当防卫啦
It was self-defense?
对
Yeah.
麦克为了救我妹妹而坐牢
Mike went to jail trying to save my sister.
但终究没救回她
But he couldn't.
我就知道他是好人
I knew he was good.
我就知道
I just knew it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
誓言很简单 千真万确
The vow is simple, really.
人们承诺要白头到老
Those who take it promise to stay together
不论顺境或逆境
for better or for worse,
不论富裕或贫穷
for richer or for poorer,
不论疾病或健康
in sickness and in health.
彼此珍惜
To honor and to cherish.
彼此忠诚
For saking all others.
直至死亡将我们分离
Until death do us part.
是啊 誓言很简单
Yes, the vow is simple.
难的是找到值得承诺的人
Finding someone worthy of such a promise is the hard part.
但只要我们能找到
But if we can,
那么幸福的生活将就此展开
that's when we begin to live happily ever after.